

CONTACT



+36 30 430 0367



vadasz.reka87@gmail.com



in https://www.linkedin.com/in/ reka-vadasz/



https://github.com/ RekaVadasz

SKILLS

















LANGUAGES

- Hungarian (native)
- English (advanced)
- German (intermediate)
- Italian (basic)

RÉKA VADÁSZ

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

ABOUT ME

My professional goal is to strengthen my skills as a junior front-end developer. I have experience mostly with front-end development (React) with a little insight into back-end operations (Node.js).

I am looking forward to develop my knowledge, learn new technologies and create beautiful and user-friendly Uls.

My Portfolio Page:

https://papaya-rugelach-54f928.netlify.app/

WORK EXPERIENCE

Financial Assistant (2018-2022)

AMS Group Kft.

Administrative Assistant (2016-2017)

Monsanto

Human Resources Officer (2015-2016)

Finesource Kft.

Customer Service Advisor (2014-2015)

Diegeo

EDUCATION

Front-End Development Course (2022)

Codecool

English Applied Linguistics, MA (2010-2013)

Eötvös Loránd University

Erasmus Scholarship - 2 semesters (2008 - 2009)

University of Cologne (Germany)

Hungarian Language and Litarature, BA (2006 - 2010)

Eötvös Loránd University